https://www.jswhorseboxes.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy - JSW Horseboxes
Horseboxes, Trailers & More Need help? Call us on 01609 772 449
Search for:
Join us
Contact Us
Book a Viewing Contact Us
×HomeAbout UsOur HistoryNewsHorseboxes &
Horse TrailersCleveland Two horseboxesOverlander HorseboxesHorse TrailersNew and
Used in StockGeneral Purpose
TrailersBatesonDebonSpecialist Fabrication
WorksServicing, Repairs
& RefurbishmentsHorsebox Servicing & RepairsHaving Ramp Problems?Trailer Service and RepairsTrailer Service RemindersInfo
GuidesFinanceHorsebox Buyers GuideHorse Trailer Buyers GuideHorse Trailer Maintenance Guide
Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyJSW Coachbuilders Ltd & JSW Trailers Privacy PolicyJSW Coachbuilders Ltd is committed to complying with the Data Protection Act 1998. This guide aims to help you understand how and why we collect information from you, who has access to it and what you rights are.Any policy changes will result in this statement being amended as appropriate. You can access the website without disclosing personal data. However, any orders will require you to provide certain details about yourself.How do we get the information and what do we collect?We receive information directly from you when you place an order or register for our email newsletter. On placing an order you will be asked to provide essential information such as your name, address, credit/debit card details, telephone numbers and email address so that we can process the order and inform you of any order status. The information also allows us to inform you of special offers and promotions.How we use the informationThe information collected is used to:Process ordersWebsite administrationMonitor customer traffic and site useage to help us develop and improve our websiteNotify you about service changes such as changes to the website, new services and special offersWhat happens to my data?JSW will never pass on any information held about its customers for the purposes above to any third parties without your consent. If you want to be removed from our database contact us by emailing us through our contact page.Security JSW takes online security very seriously. We use a server certificate to assure you of our identity and secure sockets later (SSL) to encrypt data transmissions.If you want to check our certifications visit the website and follow the following instructions depending on your internet explorer.Microsoft Internet Explorer 7 or later – click on the gold padlock at the bottom right of your browser to bring up the details of the site’s digital IDMozilla Firefox – click on the yellow padlock at the bottom left of your browser to bring up the security informationSafari –Google Chrome –The above security measures above ensure that all reasonable steps have been taken to protect your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee absolute protection and customers should be aware that that may be a small security risk when disclosing information online. We strongly advise that online shoppers take advantage of well known internet protection software for their own peace of mind.Brands We Stock…from the following leading manufacturers
Sign up for our newsletterBe the first to know. Sign up for newsletters today
SubmitAboutOur HistoryTestimonialsNewsInformationFinanceHorse Trailer Maintenance GuideHorsebox Buyers’ GuideHorsebox Servicing & RepairsExtrasCookie PolicyPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsContact Us© 2020 JSW. All Rights Reserved. Website by net*
